<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Laszlo&#39;s Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Laszlo&#39;s Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Progress on Figuring out Hugo&#39;s template system</title>
      <link>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-17-hugo-template-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-17-hugo-template-progress/</guid>
      <description>Today, finally I managed to get the page showing the way I originally envisioned.
I wanted to have the links on the left sidebar to be the content from the /content/pages/ folder, while the list on the right (main) section on the home page to show only the pages from the /content/posts/ folder. Just like a regular blog.
The trick lied in modifying two template files: layouts/_default/baseof.html and layouts/_default/list.html
The first is the overall template for the whole site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Rusty</title>
      <link>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-16-getting-rusty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-16-getting-rusty/</guid>
      <description>About 2 weeks ago, I read an article about the programming language Rust has won the most loved language in Stackoverflow survery for 2020. For 5 years in a row.
It was about 5 years ago when I looked into Go (Golang) and at that time I read a bunch of comparisions between Go and Rust. And somehow, I didn&amp;rsquo;t end up trying it. Go was great and ended up building many tools with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day</title>
      <link>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-15-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/2020-06-15-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>Today is a my own personal Independence Day. Two years ago on this day, I started a new life.
What lead up to this point is that I had a dream of making a difference in the world &amp;amp; gave up everything for it. But after a year, I had to realize that every one of my goals were thoroughly blocked and I was mired down in rules, regulations - written, spoken and un-spoken ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Fist Post with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lacikawiz.github.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>The first post with Hugo This Sunday morning I woke up early and I decided to try if I can put together a static website with Hugo and publish it with Github pages. I had been thinking about this for about a year now, since I read some articles about it. I&amp;rsquo;m very interested in making very fast loading sites, which are also simple under the hood. I also wanted to make a site where I can publish my thoughts without the noise of social networking sites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>